greatvaluevacations.com 2017-06-09

# Privacy Policy | GreatValueVacations.com

As a valued Great Value Vacations customer, your personal privacy is very important to us. We understand that booking online involves significant trust on your part. We value your trust and have made it a high priority to ensure the security and confidentiality of the personal information you provide to us. Please read this policy to learn about our privacy practices. By using this website, you are accepting the practices described in this policy.

How do I know my personal information including credit card are kept confidential and safe when I book travel on the Great Value Vacations website?  
When you book travel on the Great Value Vacations site, you do so through a secure server. The use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology means that all personal information, including your credit card number, will be encrypted as it travels from your computer to the Great Value Vacations Online Booking Engine. When received, the information is decrypted and processed in the same way as a normal credit card transaction by telephone.

If your browser supports SSL, and if you entered our site via our secure server access, then transmission of any sensitive data will be protected. If your browser does not support SSL, we recommend that you upgrade to the latest version of any browser to enhance the security of further transactions; otherwise, the transmission of your personal data may not be protected and Great Value Vacations disclaims any responsibility in this regard.

What personal information is collected when I visit the Great Value Vacations website?

We do not collect personal information about you when you browse the Great Value Vacations website. However, if you wish to book a package online with us, you will be required to provide the following information to complete the transaction:

• Name  
• Mailing and billing address  
• Credit card number and expiration date  
• Phone numbers  
• Email address

In addition, the Transportation Security Administration (TSA) requires that we collect the following information about passengers associated with every online and phone booking:

       • Full Name  
       • Gender  
       • Date of Birth

Is this personal information stored or shared by Great Value Vacations?  
Great Value Vacations will use your personal information to process your booking, to verify credit card processing and to help you manage your itinerary prior to departure. Your personal information and any records relating to your air travel will also be retained for audit functions.

Great Value Vacations does not share your personal information with any third parties.

What other types of information does Great Value Vacations collect?

Travel Companion Information. When you make a reservation for someone else through this website, we will request personal information about that individual. You should obtain the consent of other individuals prior to providing us with their personal information.  

Information from Other Sources. We also may periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about customers who book travel with us from affiliated entities, business partners and other independent third-party sources and add it to our account information. Examples of information we may receive include: updated delivery and address information, purchase history, and demographic information.

Automatic Information. We automatically collect some information about your computer when you visit this website. For example, we will collect your IP address, Web browser software (such as Firefox, Safari, or Internet Explorer), and referring website. We also may collect information about your online activity, such as trips viewed and bookings made. Our goals in collecting this automatic information include helping customize your user experience and preventing fraud.

Does the Great Value Vacations website use cookies?  
Cookies are small data text files and can be stored on your computer’s hard drive (if your Web browser permits). This website uses cookies for the following general purposes:

• To help us recognize your browser as a previous visitor  
• To determine whether you have come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website  
• To help measure and research the effectiveness of website features and offerings, advertisements, and email communications (by determining which emails you open and act upon).

Contact us  
If you have any other concerns, suggestions or questions about any issues relating to privacy on the Great Value Vacations website, please [contact us](https://new.greatvaluevacations.com/content/contact-us).
